[
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "Security professionals are tasked with the protection of persons, property, and",
		"correct": "Information",
		"options": [
			"Government buildings",
			"Employee belongings",
			"Information",
			"Military locations"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "Individuals holding an individual security licence in the province of Alberta may not refer to themselves as: ",
		"correct": "Peace officers",
		"options": [
			"Security professionals",
			"Loss prevention workers",
			"Peace officers",
			"Watchpersons"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": " Professionalism is best demonstrated by: ",
		"correct": "Peace officers",
		"options": [
			"Your conduct and deportment",
			"Loss prevention workers",
			"Peace officers",
			"Watchpersons"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "Your conduct and deportment __________________ utilized by licensed security professionals must be authorized by the Registrar",
		"correct": "Batons",
		"options": [
			"Batons",
			"Reporting forms ",
			"Post orders ",
			"Safety equipment "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "The notes in your notebook will help you: ",
		"correct": "Prepare reports for your employer and others",
		"options": [
			"a.	Prepare reports for your employer and others ",
			"b.	Avoid court testimony ",
			"c.	Obtain a security licence in another    classification ",
			"d.	Communicate non-verbally  "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "Writing profanity in your notebook is: ",
		"correct": "Acceptable when you are quoting verbatim ",
		"options": [
			"Never appropriate",
			"b.	Acceptable when you are quoting verbatim ",
			"c.	Inadmissible in court ",
			"d.	Prohibited under the Security Services and Investigator’s Act "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "A statement is usually gathered as part of the _____________ process. ",
		"correct": "Interview",
		"options": [
			"Use of force",
			"b.	Interview ",
			"c.	Verbal communication",
			"d.	Post-order "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "When you lose your security licence, you must file a written report to:",
		"correct": "The Registrar of Security programs",
		"options": [
			"a.	The police ",
			"b.	The Registrar of Security programs",
			"c.	Your supervisor ",
			"d.	The client where you lost your licence"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "A security professional in the province of Alberta must be, at minimum, _________years of age. ",
		"correct": "18",
		"options": ["a.	16", "b.	18 ", "c.	19 ", "d.	21 "]
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "A licensed security professional may perform the following tasks:",
		"correct": "All of the above",
		"options": [
			"a. 	Monitoring of alarm systems ",
			"b.	Arrest of persons found committing a crime",
			"c.	Responding to emergencies ",
			"d.	Conducting physical searches of purses,   backpacks, and other personal items",
			"All of the above"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "Protecting information may include limiting access of persons to computer equipment and data.",
		"correct": "True",
		"options": ["a.	True ", "b.	False "]
	},
    {
		"id": 12,
		"question": "An individual holding a security licence is licensed to work as a private detective when:",
		"correct": "Never ",
		"options": [ 
            "a.	Directed by the licensee’s employer ",
            "b.	The security professional is directed to  protect information", 
            "c.	The work of another employee must be covered due to illness or vacation" 
            "d.	Never "
            ]
	}
    ,
    {
		"id": 13,
		"question": "Uniform requirements for licensed security professionals are designated by:",
		"correct": "Never ",
		"options": [ 
" a. 	The Employment Standards Code and  Regulation ",
" b.	The Security Operations Standards Council ",
" The Security Services and Investigators  Act ",
 "The Alberta Association of Chiefs of Police "
 
            ]
	}
]
